A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Grants, SG 2, Series 10 FA1448
Rockefeller Archive Center
- University of Wisconsin - Bowers (20110148) (Box 61, Folder 5)
- University of Wisconsin - Bowers (20110148), 2010-2011 (Box 62, Folder 1)
- Johns Hopkins University - Anderson (20060421), 2005-2006 (Box 62, Folder 2)
- Johns Hopkins University - Anderson (20060633), 2006-2007 (Box 62, Folder 3)
- University of Maryland, Baltimore County - Stuart (20080306), 2008-2010 (Box 62, Folder 4)
- University of Maryland, Baltimore County - Stuart (20080306) - Grant Products, Proposal Development (Box 62, Folder 5)
- Virginia Commonwealth University - McCue (20100486) (Box 63, Folder 1)
- Medical University of South Carolina - Pittand (20090162), 2008-2010 (Box 63, Folder 2)
- University of Oklahoma - Nichols (20100606) (Box 63, Folder 3)
- Johnson Group Consulting, Inc. - Johnson (20100424) (Box 63, Folder 4)
- AcademyHealth - Martinez-Vidal (20100262), 2009-2010 (Box 63, Folder 5)
- International Communications Research, Inc. (ICR) - Herrmann (20080224), 2008-2009 (Box 63, Folder 6)
- International Communications Research, Inc. (ICR) - Herrmann (20080224) - Proposal (Box 64, Folder 1)
- International Communications Research, Inc. (ICR) - Herrmann (20080224) - Grant Products, 2008-2009 (Box 64, Folder 2-3)
- International Communications Research, Inc. (ICR) - Herrmann (20080224) - Correspondence (Box 64, Folder 4)
- International Communications Research, Inc. (ICR) - Herrmann (20080224) - NOLA Clinics Book 1, 2009 March (Box 64, Folder 5-6)
- International Communications Research, Inc. (ICR) - Herrmann (20080224) - NOLA Clinics Book 2, 2009 March (Box 65, Folder 1-2)
- University of Texas Health Science Center - Jaen (20070114), 2005-2010 (Box 65, Folder 3)
- University of Texas Health Science Center - Jaen (20070114) - Proposal, 2005-2007 (Box 65, Folder 4)
- University of Texas Health Science Center - Jaen (20070114) - Grant Products (Box 66, Folder 1)
- MedStar Research Institute - Miodovnik (20050044), 2003-2009 (Box 66, Folder 2-3)
- Group Health Cooperative - Wagner (20090425), 2009-2010 (Box 66, Folder 4)
- New England Medical Center Hospitals, Inc. - Irish (20070127), 2005-2007 (Box 66, Folder 5)
- New England Medical Center Hospitals, Inc. - Irish (20070127), 2005-2009 (Box 67, Folder 1)
- Massachusetts Medical Society - Kirshenbaum and Fitzgerald (20100358), 2008-2010 (Box 67, Folder 2)
- DMA Health Strategies - Lyman (20080292), 2008-2010 (Box 67, Folder 3)
- Harris Interactive - Peugh (20080154), 2008-2009 (Box 67, Folder 4)
- Center for Health Policy Development - Kaye and Purrington (20100423) (Box 67, Folder 5)
- Visiting Nurse Service of New York - Feldman (20100275), 2009-2012 (Box 67, Folder 6)
- Visiting Nurse Service of New York - Feldman (20100275) - Proposal Development, Correspondence, 2010-2012 (Box 68, Folder 1)
- Visiting Nurse Service of New York - Feldman (20100275) - Articles and Grant Products, 2010-2012 (Box 68, Folder 2)
- AcademyHealth - Martinez-Vidal (20090260), 2008-2009 (Box 68, Folder 3)
- President and Fellows of Harvard College - Chernew (20090562), 2009-2011 (Box 68, Folder 4)
- Trustees of Boston University - Cohen (20070209), 2007-2010 (Box 68, Folder 5)
- Boston University - Health Policy Institute - Cohen (20050472), 2005-2009 (Box 69, Folder 1)
- AcademyHealth - Gauthier (20050605) - Commission on High Performance Health System, 2005-2008 (Box 69, Folder 2)
- AcademyHealth - Gauthier (20060619) - Commission on High Performance Health System, 2005-2007 (Box 69, Folder 3)
- Commission on High Performance Health System - Gauthier - Presentations (Box 69, Folder 4-6)
- Commission on High Performance Health System - Gauthier - Site Visits, 2004-2005 (Box 70, Folder 1)
- Commission on High Performance Health System - Gauthier - Conferences and Meetings, 2004-2006 (Box 70, Folder 2)
- Commission on High Performance Health System - Gauthier - Articles of Personal Interest (Box 70, Folder 3)
- Commission on High Performance Health System - Gauthier - State Program Plan Development (Box 70, Folder 4-5)
- Commission on High Performance Health System - Gauthier - Minnesota Smart Buy (Box 70, Folder 6)
- Commission on High Performance Health System - Gauthier - CPOE Wendy Everett (Box 71, Folder 1)
- Commission on High Performance Health System - Gauthier - PPO Hedis Reporting (Box 71, Folder 2)
- Commission on High Performance Health System - Gauthier - Minyard Case Study (Box 71, Folder 3)
- Commission on High Performance Health System - Gauthier - WI Collaborative for Health Care Quality (Box 71, Folder 4)
- Commission on High Performance Health System - Gauthier - Premium Assistance Programs Learnings from IL Rebate (Box 71, Folder 5)
- Commission on High Performance Health System - Gauthier - Denver Health Case Study (Box 71, Folder 6)
- Commission on High Performance Health System - Gauthier - Commission Paper Colorado Health Care System (Box 71, Folder 7)
- Center for Studying Health System Change - Cunningham (20070655) (Box 71, Folder 8)
- Urban Institute - Dorn (20090631) (Box 72, Folder 1)
- Brigham and Women's Hospital - Choudry (20080114), 2008-2012 (Box 72, Folder 2-3)
- Economic Policy Institute - Gould (20070682), 2007-2009 (Box 72, Folder 4)
- Commonwealth Fund - Collins (20070395), 2007-2009 (Box 72, Folder 5)
- Health Policy Research - Horton (20070683) (Box 72, Folder 6)
- The Lewin Group - Sheils (20070719), 2007-2012 (Box 72, Folder 7)
- Congressional Health Care Bills - 110th Congress, 2007-2008 (Box 72, Folder 8)
- Health Policy Research - Horton (20080181) (Box 73, Folder 1)
- AcademyHealth - Helms (20050090), 2003-2006 (Box 73, Folder 2)
- AcademyHealth - Helms (20050090) - Proposal Development (Box 73, Folder 3)
- AcademyHealth - Helms (20050090) - Administration and Correspondence, 2004-2009 (Box 73, Folder 4)
- Commonwealth Fund - Collins (20050081), 2005-2010 (Box 73, Folder 5)
- Commonwealth Fund - Collins (20050081) - Congressional Bills, 2009 (Box 73, Folder 6)
- Health Policy Research - Horton (20090595) (Box 73, Folder 7)
- Health Reform 2009-2010 - Merged Senate Bill (Box 74, Folder 1)
- Health Reform 2009-2010 - Kaiser Premium Subsidy Calculator (Box 74, Folder 2)
- Health Reform 2009-2010 - Congressional Updates 2009 (Box 74, Folder 3)
- Health Reform 2009-2010 - Congressional Bills - Coverage Report (Box 74, Folder 4)
- The Lewin Group - Sheils (20090610) (Box 74, Folder 5)
- Center for Health Policy Development - Kaye (20100518) (Box 74, Folder 6)
- Nuffield Trust - Owen (20010152), 1999-2001 (Box 74, Folder 7)
- Brigham and Women's Hospital - Kaushal (20050363), 1999-2001 (Box 74, Folder 8)
- University of Maryland - Milligan (20050272) (Box 74, Folder 9)
- Henry Ford Health System - Nerenz (20030109), 2003-2005 (Box 75, Folder 1)
- Henry Ford Health System - Nerenz (20030109) - Proposal Development, 2002 (Box 75, Folder 2)
- Henry Ford Health System - Nerenz (20030109) - Communication and Grant Products, 2003-2005 (Box 75, Folder 3)
- American College of Physicians - Barr (20070791), 2006-2010 (Box 75, Folder 4)
- American College of Physicians - Barr (20070791) - Grant Products (Box 75, Folder 5)
- New York University (NYU) - Weiztman (20040709), 2003-2008 (Box 76, Folder 1)
- President and Fellows of Harvard College - Reede (20050635), 2005-2009 (Box 76, Folder 2)
- President and Fellows of Harvard College - Reede (20050635) - Grant Products, 2007-2008 (Box 76, Folder 3)
- Illinois Chapter of American Academy of Pediatrics - Allen (20080148), 2007-2010 (Box 76, Folder 4-5)
- Research Foundation of the State University of New York - Pati (20110390), 2011-2012 (Box 77, Folder 1)
- Primary Care Development Corporation - Simino-Boyce (20050296), 2005-2009 (Box 77, Folder 2)
- Harvard - Society of General Internal Medicine, Depatment of Health Care Policy - Landon (20080371) - Proposal and Grant Products, 2008-2009 (Box 77, Folder 3)
- Harvard - Reede (20031300) - Grant Products (Box 77, Folder 4)
- Harvard - Reede (20031300) - Administration and Communications, 2004-2005 (Box 77, Folder 5)
- Massachusetts General Hospital - Kaushal (20020218), 2000-2002 (Box 77, Folder 6)
- Massachusetts General Hospital - Kaushal (20020218) - Proposal and Grant Products, 2001-2002 (Box 78, Folder 1)
- Harvard School of Public Health - Mello (20020530), 2000-2004 (Box 78, Folder 2)
- Harvard School of Public Health - Mello (20020530) - Proposal, 2001-2002 (Box 78, Folder 3)
- Harvard School of Public Health - Mello (20020530) - Grant Products, 2003 (Box 78, Folder 4)
- Harvard Pilgrim Health Care - Samandari (20010418), 2001-2004 (Box 78, Folder 5)
- Harvard Pilgrim Health Care - Samandari (20010418) - Grant Products (Box 78, Folder 6)
- Harvard Pilgrim Health Care - Samandari (20010418) - Proposal, 2001-2002 (Box 79, Folder 1)
- Regents of the University of California (San Francisco) - Miller (20030338), 2003-2005 (Box 79, Folder 2)
- Regents of the University of California (San Francisco) - Miller (20030338) - Proposal, Grant Products, 2002-2003 (Box 79, Folder 3)
- Harvard School of Public Health - Rosenthal (20030386), 2003-2006 (Box 79, Folder 4)
- Harvard School of Public Health - Rosenthal (20030386) - Proposal (Box 79, Folder 5)
- Harvard School of Public Health - Rosenthal (20030386) - Grant Products, 2005 (Box 80, Folder 1)
- Massachusetts General Hospital - Blumenthal (20031255), 2003-2006 (Box 80, Folder 2)
- Massachusetts General Hospital - Blumenthal (20031255) - Grant Products (Box 80, Folder 3)
- Massachusetts General Hospital - Blumenthal (20040672), 2003-2007 (Box 80, Folder 4)
- Massachusetts General Hospital - Blumenthal (20040672) - Proposal (Box 80, Folder 5)
- Massachusetts General Hospital - Blumenthal (20040672) - Grant Products, 2004-2005 (Box 80, Folder 6-7)
- University of North Carolina - Kilpatrick (20040376) (Box 81, Folder 1)
- University of North Carolina - Kilpatrick (20040376) - Grant Products (Box 81, Folder 2-3)
- Regents of the University of California - Shortell (20050334), 2005-2010 (Box 81, Folder 4)
- Regents of the University of California - Shortell (20050334) (Box 82, Folder 1-2)
- Thomas Jefferson University - Nash (20030104), 2002-2005 (Box 82, Folder 3-4)
- American Board of Internal Medicine Foundation - Wolfson (20030071), 2002-2006 (Box 82, Folder 5)
- American Board of Internal Medicine Foundation - Wolfson (20030071) (Box 83, Folder 1-2)
- Economic and Social Institute - Meyer (20030102), 2001-2004 (Box 83, Folder 3-4)
- Economic and Social Institute - Meyer (20030102), 2003-2004 (Box 84, Folder 1)
- Brigham and Women's Hospital Inc. - Gandi (20010373), 2001-2002 (Box 84, Folder 2)
- Brigham and Women's Hospital Inc. - Gandi (20010373) - Administration and Budget (Box 84, Folder 3)
- Brigham and Women's Hospital Inc. - Gandi (20010373) - Grant Products (Box 84, Folder 4)
- Brigham and Women's Hospital Inc. - Gandi (20010373) - Proposal (Box 84, Folder 5)
- Brigham and Women's Hospital Inc. - Gandi (20010373) - Articles, 1999-2007 (Box 84, Folder 6)
- National Committee for Quality Assurance - Torda (20090698) (Box 85, Folder 1)
- Health Systems Research Inc. (20060458) - Bartlett (Box 85, Folder 2)
- Health Systems Research Inc. (20060458) - Bartlett, 2007 (Box 85, Folder 3)
- National Quality Forum - Winkler (20060735), 2006-2007 (Box 85, Folder 4)
- National Quality Forum - Winkler (20060735) (Box 85, Folder 5)
- Regents of the University of California - Miller (20070042) (Box 86, Folder 1)
- Society for General Internal Medicine - Karlson (20060275) (Box 86, Folder 2)
- Trustees of Dartmouth College - Wasson (20040204), 2003-2010 (Box 86, Folder 3)
- Trustees of Dartmouth College - Wasson (20040204), 2003-2010 (Box 86, Folder 4)
- Bridges to Excellence - de Brantes (20070095), 2005-2007 (Box 86, Folder 5)
- Bridges to Excellence - de Brantes (20070095) - Grant Products (Box 87, Folder 1)
- Bridges to Excellence - de Brantes (20070095) - Proposal (Box 87, Folder 2)
- Bridges to Excellence - de Brantes (20070095) (Box 87, Folder 3)
- Institute for Healthcare Improvement - Boutwell (20080047) (Box 87, Folder 4)
- Institute for Healthcare Improvement - Boutwell (20080047) - Planning (Box 87, Folder 5)
- Institute for Healthcare Improvement - Boutwell (20080047) - Narrative Reports (Box 87, Folder 6)
- Institute for Healthcare Improvement - Boutwell (20080047) - Grant Products (Box 88, Folder 1)
- Institute for Healthcare Improvement - Boutwell (20090317) (Box 88, Folder 2)
- Institute for Healthcare Improvement - Boutwell (20090317) - Grant Products (Box 88, Folder 3)
- Institute for Healthcare Improvement - Boutwell (20100514) (Box 88, Folder 4)
- Institute for Healthcare Improvement - Boutwell (20100514) - Grant Products (Box 88, Folder 5)
- Institute for Healthcare Improvement - Boutwell (20100514) - Grant Products (Box 89, Folder 1)
- University of North Carolina - Leatherman (20040673) (Box 89, Folder 2)
- University of North Carolina - Leatherman (20040673) - Proposal (Box 89, Folder 3)
- University of North Carolina - Kilpatrick (20031296), 2003-2004 (Box 89, Folder 4)
- University of North Carolina - Kilpatrick (20031296) - Proposal (Box 89, Folder 5)
- University of North Carolina - Kilpatrick (20031296) - Grant Products (Box 90, Folder 1)
- University of North Carolina - Kilpatrick (20031296) (Box 90, Folder 2-3)
- Harbage Consulting - Harbage (20080271), 2008-2009 (Box 90, Folder 4)
- Washington University - Gowrisankaran (20070068), 2007-2011 (Box 90, Folder 5)
- Washington University - Gowrisankaran (20070068), 2007-2011 (Box 91, Folder 1)
- Trustees of Columbia University - Sampat (20100119), 2009-2012 (Box 91, Folder 2)
- National Opinion Research - Gabel (20090612), 2009-2010 (Box 91, Folder 3)
- Education and Research Fund of the Employee Benefit Research Institute - Fronstin (20100553), 2010-2012 (Box 91, Folder 4)
- Trustees of Columbia University - Glied (20090137), 2008-2010 (Box 91, Folder 5)
- Education and Research Fund of the Employee Benefit Research Institute - Fronstin (20100004), 2009-2011 (Box 91, Folder 6)
- University of Kansas Center for Research, Inc. - Hall (20100361), 2010-2012 (Box 92, Folder 1)
- President and Fellows of Harvard College - Ayanian (20010558), 2001-2003 (Box 92, Folder 2)
- Rand Corporation - Buntin (20080206), 2008-2010 (Box 92, Folder 3)
- Trustees of Columbia University - Glied (20070776), 2007-2010 (Box 92, Folder 4)
- George Washington University - Rosenbaum (20100559), 2010-2011 (Box 92, Folder 5)
- National Opinion Research - Gabel (20070774), 2007-2010 (Box 93, Folder 1)
- Massachusetts General Hospital - Perrin (20020823), 2001-2004 (Box 93, Folder 2)
- National Committee for Quality Assurance - Tonda (20020803), 2001-2003 (Box 93, Folder 3)
- Midwest Business Group on Health - Mortimer (20020804), 2001-2002 (Box 93, Folder 4)
- Midwest Business Group on Health - Mortimer (20020804) - Grant Products, 2002-2003 (Box 94, Folder 1)
- Midwest Business Group on Health - Mortimer (20020804) - Proposal (Box 94, Folder 2)
- Accreditation Council for Graduate Medical Education (20020796) - Leach, 2002-2003 (Box 94, Folder 3-4)
- Accreditation Council for Graduate Medical Education (20020796) - Leach, 2002 December 7-8 (Box 95, Folder 1)
- Trustees of Dartmouth College - Wasson (20010490), 2001-2002 (Box 95, Folder 2-3)
- National Committee for Quality Assurance - Pawlson (20010750), 2001-2002 (Box 95, Folder 4)
- National Committee for Quality Assurance - Pawlson (20010750) - Grant Products (Box 96, Folder 1)
- Primary Care Development Corporation - Kotelchuck (20020330), 2001-2004 (Box 96, Folder 2-3)
- Massachusetts Health Quality Partners (20060112) - Proposal, Grant Products, 2005-2015 (Box 96, Folder 4)
- The Urban Institute - Berenson (20060093), 2005-2006 (Box 97, Folder 1)
- The Urban Institute - Berenson (20060093) - Grant Products (Box 97, Folder 2-3)
- President and Fellows of Harvard College - Schneider (20060551) (Box 97, Folder 4)
- President and Fellows of Harvard College - Schneider (20060551) - Grant Products (Box 97, Folder 5)
- President and Fellows of Harvard College - Schneider (20060551) - Proposal Materials (Box 97, Folder 6)
- University of California, Irvine - Kaplan (20030101), 2003-2010 (Box 98, Folder 1)
- University of California, Irvine - Kaplan (20030101) - Proposal Development (Box 98, Folder 2)
- University of California, Irvine - Kaplan (20030101) - Grant Products (Box 98, Folder 3)
- The Leapfrog Group for Patient Safety - Deblanco (20060549) (Box 98, Folder 4)
- The Leapfrog Group for Patient Safety - Deblanco (20060549) - Grant Products (Box 98, Folder 5)
- President and Fellows of Harvard College - Epstein (20070132), 2006-2009 (Box 99, Folder 1)
- President and Fellows of Harvard College - Epstein (20070132) - Grant Products (Box 99, Folder 2)
- National Initiative for Children's Health Care Quality (20030325), 2002-2003 (Box 99, Folder 3)
- Kaiser Foundation Health Plan, Inc. - Tollen (20070382), 2005-2007 (Box 99, Folder 4)
- Alliance for Health Reform - Howard (20100516), 2010-2012 (Box 99, Folder 5)
- Alliance for Health Reform - Howard (20100516) - Retreat Materials and Narrative Report (Box 99, Folder 6)
- Alliance for Health Reform - Howard (20100516) - Congressional Briefings, 2010 October (Box 99, Folder 7)
- Alliance for Health Reform - Howard (20100516) - Congressional Briefings, 2010 December (Box 99, Folder 8)
- Alliance for Health Reform - Howard (20100516) - Congressional Briefings, 2011 April-July (Box 100, Folder 1-2)
- University of North Carolina - Kilpatrick - Business Case for Quality in Health Care, 2004-2015 (Box 100, Folder 3-4)
- Lowell, City of - Campbell (2083-2), 1988-2015 (Box 101, Folder 1)
- Institute for Healthcare Improvement - Goldmann (20110267), 2011-2012 (Box 101, Folder 2)
- Institute for Healthcare Improvement - Goldmann (20110267) - Grant Products (Box 101, Folder 3)
- Health Management Associates - Silow-Carroll (20050547), 2005-2006 (Box 101, Folder 4)
- Johns Hopkins University - Powe (20050277), 2005-2009 (Box 102, Folder 1)
- Johns Hopkins University - Powe (20050277) - Administration (Box 102, Folder 2)
- Park Nicollet Institute - Fowles (20060073), 2005-2008 (Box 102, Folder 3-5)
- Park Nicollet Institute - Fowles (20060073), 2006-2007 (Box 103, Folder 1)
- Boston University - Health Policy Institute - Cohen (20070397), 2007-2008 (Box 103, Folder 2)
- National Academy of Sciences - Eisenberg (20070083), 2005-2007 (Box 103, Folder 3)
- Rochester Individual Practice Association (20070229) - Beckman, 2005-2007 (Box 103, Folder 4)
- The Urban Institute - Zuckerman (20070197), 2006-2007 (Box 103, Folder 5)
- American Medical Infomatics Association - Detmer (20070835), 2007-2009 (Box 104, Folder 1)
- Center for Studying Health System Change - O'Malley (20070668), 2007-2010 (Box 104, Folder 2)
- Yale University - Bradley (20080041), 2008-2010 (Box 104, Folder 3)
- Wisconsin Collaborative for Healthcare Quality - Clough (20070507), 2007-2008 (Box 104, Folder 4)
- National Committee for Quality Assurance - Roski (20070143), 2005-2007 (Box 104, Folder 5)
- President and Fellows of Harvard College - Marcus (20040072), 2003-2004 (Box 105, Folder 1)
- Employee Benefit Research Institute - Fronstin (20030560), 2003-2004 (Box 105, Folder 2-3)
- Regents of the University of California - Miller (20070495) (Box 105, Folder 4)
- Regents of the University of California - Miller (20070495) - Proposal, 2007-2009 (Box 105, Folder 5)
- New York University (NYU) - Cortes (20120048), 2011-2013 (Box 106, Folder 1)
- LeadingAge, Inc. - Naylor, Phillips (20110329) (Box 106, Folder 2)
- LeadingAge, Inc. - Naylor (20110329) - Proposal Development (Box 106, Folder 3)
- LeadingAge, Inc. - Naylor (20110329) (Box 106, Folder 4)
- Board of Regents of the University of Wisconsin - Olson (20100611), 2009-2013 (Box 107, Folder 1)
- University of North Carolina (Chapel Hill) - Zimmerman (20110457), 2010-2013 (Box 107, Folder 2)
- Dobson DaVanzo and Associates - Dobson (20110397), 2011-2013 (Box 107, Folder 3)
- AcademyHealth - Brookstein (20120049), 2011-2012 (Box 107, Folder 4)
- American Health Care Association (AHCA) - Gifford (20120354), 2012-2013 (Box 108, Folder 1)
- University of Pittsburgh - Castle (20120204), 2011-2013 (Box 108, Folder 2)
- National Senior Citizens Law Center - Prindiville (20120075), 2011-2012 (Box 108, Folder 3)
- Princeton Survey Research Associates International - McIntosh (20090287) - Young Adult Survey, 2008-2010 (Box 108, Folder 4)
- Young Adult Survey (20090287) (Box 108, Folder 5)
- Young Adult Survey (20090287) (Box 109, Folder 1-2)
- Massachusetts Department of Public Health - Bonner (20100525) (Box 109, Folder 3)
- LeadingAge, Inc. - Benner (20100554) - Nursing Home Pilot Summary (Box 109, Folder 4)
- Center for Medicare Advocacy - Edelman (20130001) (Box 110, Folder 1)
- Altarum Institute - Lynn (20110456), 2011-2012 (Box 110, Folder 2)
- Premier Research Institute - Kroch (20110331), 2010-2013 (Box 110, Folder 3)
- President and Fellows of Harvard College - Grabowski (20100274), 2009-2012 (Box 110, Folder 4)
- AARP Foundation - Reinhard (20100273), 2010-2011 (Box 110, Folder 5)
- AARP Foundation - Reinhard (20100273) - Articles and Background, 2006-2011 (Box 111, Folder 1-2)
- AARP Foundation - Reinhard (20100273) - Proposal Development (Box 111, Folder 3)
- AARP Foundation - Reinhard (20100273) - Grant Products, 2010-2011 (Box 111, Folder 4)
- AARP Foundation - Reinhard (20100273) - Grant Products, 2010-2011 (Box 112, Folder 1)
- National Commission for Quality Long-Term Care - Koren, 2007 (Box 112, Folder 2)
- National Academy of Sciences - Behany (20070140) - Grant Products, 2008 (Box 112, Folder 3)
- Board of Regents of the University of Wisconsin - Zimmerman (20020672, 20070611) (Box 112, Folder 4)
- Rhode Island Department of Health - Gifford (20070134) - Grant Products, 2005 (Box 112, Folder 5)
- National Senior Citizens Law Center - Carlson (20040839) - Grant Products, 2005 (Box 112, Folder 6)
- Harris Interactive, Inc. - Peugh (20060486) - National Survey of Nursing Homes (Box 113, Folder 1-2)
- Independent Production Fund - Zbar (95-49) - Residents Have Answers (Box 113, Folder 3)
- Independent Production Fund - Zbar (95-49) - Residents Have the Answers: Improving Quality of Life in Long-term Care, 2001; VHS; 33 minutes (Box 1, Tape AV 11751)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Access copy currently unavailable. Please see a RAC archivist for further instruction.
- Harris Interactive, Inc. - Study No. 27963 - National Study of Nursing Homes, 2007 (Box 113, Folder 4)
- Harris Interactive, Inc. - Study No. 27963 - National Study of Nursing Homes, 2007 (Box 114, Folder 1)
- Mount Sinai School of Medicine of New York University (NYU) - Meier (98017) - Quality Outcomes for Care at the End of Life (Box 114, Folder 2-3)
- Yale University - Inouye (20040073) (Box 114, Folder 4)
- Yale University - Inouye (20040073) - Volunteer Training Manual (Box 114, Folder 5)
- Yale University - Inouye (20040073) - Organizational and Procedural Manual, Volume II (Box 114, Folder 6)
- Yale University - Inouye (20040073) - Organizational and Procedural Manual, Volume I (Box 115, Folder 1)
- Urban Institute - Moon (990204) (Box 115, Folder 2)
- University of Wisconsin (20030240) (Box 115, Folder 3)
- University of Minnesota (20040420) (Box 115, Folder 4)
- University of Minnesota (20030388) (Box 115, Folder 5)
- University of Minnesota - Kane (20030501) (Box 115, Folder 6)
- National Committee to Prevent Child Abuse - Donnelly (PDF 96698), 1995-1997 (Box 115, Folder 7)
- Employee Benefit Research Institute - Salisbury (20060170), 2005-2006 (Box 115, Folder 8)
- Massachusetts General Hospital - Donelan (20070079), 2006-2007 (Box 115, Folder 9)
- Virginia Commonwealth University - Bradley (20060322), 2005-2007 (Box 115, Folder 10)